# 🐛 Bug
## Information
"mrm8488/bert-spanish-cased-finetuned-ner"
Language I am using the model on (English, Chinese ...): Spanish
The problem arises when using:
  * the official example scripts: (give details below)
  * my own modified scripts: (give details below)
The tasks I am working on is:
  * an official GLUE/SQUaD task: (give the name)
  * my own task or dataset: (give details below)
## To reproduce
Steps to reproduce the behavior:
  1. create a `ner` pipeline
  2. pass flag `grouped_entities`
  3. entities are not grouped as expected see sample below
    NER_MODEL = "mrm8488/bert-spanish-cased-finetuned-ner"
    nlp_ner = pipeline("ner", model=NER_MODEL,
                       grouped_entities=True,
                       tokenizer=(NER_MODEL, {"use_fast": False}))
    t = """Consuelo Araújo Noguera, ministra de cultura del presidente Andrés Pastrana (1998.2002) fue asesinada por las Farc luego de haber permanecido secuestrada por algunos meses."""
    ner(t)
    >>> 
    [ {'entity_group': 'B-PER', 'score': 0.901019960641861, 'word': 'Consuelo'}, 
     {'entity_group': 'I-PER', 'score': 0.9990904808044434, 'word': 'Araújo Noguera'}, 
     {'entity_group': 'B-PER', 'score': 0.9998136162757874, 'word': 'Andrés'}, 
     {'entity_group': 'I-PER', 'score': 0.9996985991795858, 'word': 'Pastrana'}, 
     {'entity_group': 'B-ORG', 'score': 0.9989739060401917, 'word': 'Far'}]
## Expected behavior
### Inconsistent grouping
I expect the first two items of the given sample( `B-PER`, and `I-PER`) to be
grouped. As they are contiguous tokens and correspond to a single entity spot.
It seems the current code does not take into account `B` and `I` tokens.
expected output:
     {'entity_group': 'I-PER', 'score': 0.9990904808044434, 'word': ' Consuelo Araújo Noguera'}, 
     {'entity_group': 'I-PER', 'score': 0.9998136162757874, 'word': 'Andrés Pastrana'}, 
     {'entity_group': 'B-ORG', 'score': 0.9989739060401917, 'word': 'Farc'}]
### Lost tokens?
for the same input, passing `grouped_entities=False` generates the following
output:
    [
    {'word': 'Cons', 'score': 0.9994944930076599, 'entity': 'B-PER', 'index': 1},
    {'word': '##uelo', 'score': 0.802545428276062, 'entity': 'B-PER', 'index': 2}, 
    {'word': 'Ara', 'score': 0.9993102550506592, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 3}, 
    {'word': '##új', 'score': 0.9993743896484375, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 4}, 
    {'word': '##o', 'score': 0.9992871880531311, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 5}, 
    {'word': 'No', 'score': 0.9993029236793518, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 6}, 
    {'word': '##guera', 'score': 0.9981776475906372, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 7}, 
    {'word': 'Andrés', 'score': 0.9998136162757874, 'entity': 'B-PER', 'index': 15}, 
    {'word': 'Pas', 'score': 0.999740719795227, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 16}, 
    {'word': '##tran', 'score': 0.9997414350509644, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 17}, 
    {'word': '##a', 'score': 0.9996136426925659, 'entity': 'I-PER', 'index': 18}, 
    {'word': 'Far', 'score': 0.9989739060401917, 'entity': 'B-ORG', 'index': 28}, 
    {'word': '##c', 'score': 0.7188423275947571, 'entity': 'I-ORG', 'index': 29}]
when using `grouped_entities` the last entity `word` (`##c`) got lost, it is
not even considered as a different group
` {'entity_group': 'B-ORG', 'score': 0.9989739060401917, 'word': 'Far'}]`
## Environment info
  * `transformers` version: 2.11.0
  * Platform: OSX
  * Python version: 3.7
  * PyTorch version (GPU?): 1.5.0
  * Tensorflow version (GPU?):
  * Using GPU in script?: no
  * Using distributed or parallel set-up in script?: no